# Andja Zelenbaba

Self-taught front end developer, currently seeking an entry level position or internship opportunity to improve my coding skills.

- zelenbaba.andja@gmail.com 

  Stara Pazova 

  +381 652040432
- https://github.com/andjared

## **FREELANCE PROJECTS**

Dr Vo Shop - https://drvoshop.com/

This is a web shop for small business. Worked in a small team involved in front end development. Some of my tasks included pagination, CRUD operations, handling form data, drag and drop feature, etc. This project is live, but still in development. Tech stack: React.js, Next.js on frontend, PHP on backend.

Land Essence - https://landessence.netlify.app/

This is a website for landscape architecture studio. Worked independently on the entire application with features like multi-language selection, email form, gallery, animations, etc.

Tech stack: React.js.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Ministry of Interior, Department for missing persons, Belgrade - Police Inspector

December 2017 - May 2022

- Administrative, operational and field activities related to missing persons
- Department management in the absence of the Chief of the

Department, producing daily and monthly reports

Driving school Vidana, Belgrade - Office Administrator

October 2016 - June 2017

- Client communication, business correspondence, contracts and billing
- Office supplies procurement



#### **TECH SKILLS**

React, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, Git

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Criminal
Investigations and Police - Ba in
Criminalistics

(Belgrade, 2012-2017)

Valjevo Gymnasium, Course Social Sciences and Linguistic

(Valjevo 2008-2012)

### **ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES**

**22nd OSCE Ministerial Council:**Volunteer in planning and organization (December 2015, Belgrade)

Forum for Diplomacy and International Relations, Faculty of Law: Course Participant (February 2015 - December 2015, Belgrade)